wispolitics.com 2001-04-18

# WisPolitics.com : Masthead

**_Privacy Policy_**

**1)What information is collected by WisPolitics Publishing?**

Certain information is gathered from users of the following services (go to the subscription page for each service to view what information is collected):

  * WisPolitics Subscriber Services (including the WisPolitics News Summary and the WisPolitics Report);

Personal information provided when subscribing to these services is only collected when you complete a request for the service.

In addition, our site automatically collects certain usage information about the number and frequency of visitors to WisPolitics.com and its subsections.

**2)What use is made of the information collected?**

Information collected is used primarily to deliver and promote the products and publications of WisPolitics Publishing. However, from time to time third parties may request to share information about their products with you based on WisPolitics demographic data. In these cases, the third party may either present products or services to WisPolitics.com users via on-site promotion or via mailings that will be administered by WisPolitics Publishing. But under no circumstances will those third parties have access to the personal information of WisPolitics subscribers or users.

**3)Will information be shared?**

Only demographic and usage data compiled by WisPolitics Publishing will be shared with third parties; that is, no personal information of users or subscribers will be shared unless we are legally required to do so.

**4)Whom do I contact with questions about this policy and the information that has been collected?**

Questions about the WisPolitics Publishing privacy policy should be directed to [info@wispolitics.com](mailto:info@wispolitics.com), with "PRIVACY" in the message header. Any questions regarding information collected about specific users--including updates to such information--should be sent to the same address

**Statement of Consent**

By using this website, users consent to the collection and use of information as described in the above policy. If WisPolitics Publishing changes its privacy policy, such changes will be clearly indicated on this page so that users are continually aware of our practices.
